Guide to the Sophocles Papas papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: 1987 Accession
  - Mary Elizabeth Clark (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Bass Clef Note Speller
  - Various Composers (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Folk-Songs with Guitar Chords
  - D. C. Dounis (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Fundamental Trill Studies on a Scientific Basis
  - George C. Economides (Box 8, Folder 7)
    The Study of the Guitar Simplified
  - Merle Montgomery (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Music Theory Papers (Third Set) - Sight and Sound
  - Elliot Sweetland (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Spanish Guitar Note Speller
  - John W. Schaum (Box 8, Folder 10)
    John W. Schaum Theory Lessons: Book 3
  - Alessandro Scarlatti (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Gavotte for Guitar Solo
  - Domenico Scarlatti (Box 8, Folder 12)
    9 Sonatas
  - Domenic Scarlatti (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Sonata L 238
  - Augustin Lauro (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Two Venezuelan Pieces for Guitar: 1. Valse Criollo, 2. Pavana
  - Raul Borges (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Six Venezuelan Pieces: Volume I - 1. Valse Venezolano, 2. Estudio, 3. Cancion de Cuna
  - G. F. Handel (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mateo Albeniz (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Six Pieces: Volume I - 1. Prelude in C, 2. Entrata, 3. Little Fantasia
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Six Pieces: Volume II - 1. Prelude, 2. Bist du Bei Mir, 3. Petite Courante
  - Various Composers (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Album of Guitar Solos
  - Guido Santorsola (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Three Airs of Court: 1. Preludio, 2. Aria, 3. Finale
  - Albert Harris (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Suite: 7 Pieces
  - Jeffrey Meyerriecks (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Four Preludes: 1. August, 2. Fantasy on a Child's Song
  - Jeffrey Meyerriecks (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Canonic Variations on the names "Sophocles and Mercia"
  - Francisco Araujo (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Virtuoso Waltz No. 1
  - Carlos Alberto P. Fonseca (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Seven Brazilian Etudes
  - Niccolo Paganini (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Grand Sonata
  - Andres Segovia (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Slur Exercises and Chromatic Octaves
  - Enrique Granados (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Valses Poeticos
  - George Frideric Handel (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Concerto in A Major
  - Maurice Ravel (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Pavane Pour une Enfante Defunte
  - Oscar Chilesotti (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Lute Solo
  - Ludwig Van Beethoven (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Two Bagatelles
  - John W. Duarte (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Simple Variations on "Las Folias"
  - Harold Bellman Green (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Folk Tune Fugue for Two Guitars
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Largo from Cantata No. 156
  - Isaac Albinez (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Cordoba
  - Unknown Composer (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Five Solos for Guitar
  - Miguel Llobet (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Five Catalan Melodies
  - Sophacles Papas (Box 8, Folder 40)
    The Complete Tremolo Book for the Guitar
  - Joao, Guimaraes (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Sounds of Bells
  - J. Munoz Molleda (Box 8, Folder 42)
    Differencias Sobre un Tema
  - Eduardo Grau (Box 8, Folder 43)
    La Fuente de Nie Pastrie
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 44)
    Sonata II: Volume I - Grave, Fuga
  - Andres Segovia (Box 8, Folder 45)
    Two Pieces: 1. Estudio, 2. Humorada
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Sonata II: Volume II - Andante, Allegro
  - Claude Debussy (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Clair De Lune for Two Guitars
  - Joseph Haydn (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Andante and Menuet
  - Modest Mussorgsky (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Old Castle
  - Enrique Granados (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Two Spanish Dances: 1. Fandango No. 3, 2. Rondalla Aragonesa No. 6
  - Edward Grieg (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Peasant's Song and Waltz, Op. 12
  - Fernando Sor (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Sixty Short Pieces for Guitar: Vol. I, Numbers 1-38
  - Fernando Sor (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Sixty Short Pieces for Guitar: Vol. II, Numbers 39-60
  - Antonio Vivaldi (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Concerto in D
  - Frederic Chopin (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Two Preludes for Guitar Solo
  - Luys Milan (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Six Pavanas
  - Domenico Scarlatti (Box 9, Folder 12)
    9 Sonatas: Volume II
  - Frederic Chopin (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Three Preludes
  - Daniel Purcell (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Sarabande
  - Unknown Composer (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Spanish Romance
  - Andres Segovia (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Diatonic Major and Minor Scales
  - Dionisio Aguado (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Arpeggio Studies
  - Manuel Ponce (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Two Pieces: I. Scherzino Mexicano, II. Giga Melancolica
  - Unknown Composer (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Greensleeves
  - Various Composers (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Five Solos for the Hawaiian Guitar
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Method for the Classic Guitar: Volume I Primer
  - Fernando Sor (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Folias de Espana
  - Stephen Foster (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Jeannie with the Light Brown Hair / Country Gardens
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Six Easy Flamenco Variations
  - Unknown Composer (Box 9, Folder 25)
    El Noy De La Mare
  - Andres Segovia (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 27)
    American Fantasy: A Medley for Tenor Banjo Solo
  - Franz Listz and Ludwig Van Beethoven (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Two Short Pieces
  - Ivanovici (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Danube Waves
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Malaguena
  - Various Composers (Box 9, Folder 31)
    The Highwayman and 12 Other Folk Songs
  - Alessandro Scarlatti (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Gavotte
  - Joseph Haydn and Francisco Tarrega (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Andante
  - Johann Kaspar Mertz (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Tarantella
  - Hector Villa-Lobos (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Choros
  - Various Composers (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Two Easy Christmas Carols for Guitar
  - Various Composers (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Student Guitarist's Delight: Volume 1
  - Various Composers (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Student Guitarist's Delight: Volume 2
  - Marvin Falcon (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Greek Dance and Lamet
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 40)
    Method for the Classic Guitar: New Revised and Enlarged Edition
  - Elizabeth P. Smith (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Smith's Theory Book for Guitarist Covering All Scales and Intervals
  - John R. Griggs (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Position Etudes for Plectrum Guitar
  - Various Composers (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Twenty Easy Pieces
  - Andres Segovia (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Papas' Flamenco Solos for Guitar
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Sylvia Waltz
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Bach Album: 14 Pieces by J. S. Bach for Guitar
  - Frederic Chopin (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Chopin Etude: Currently Featured as "No Other Love"
  - William Foden (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Six Short Pieces
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Duet Etude for Two Guitars
  - Jose Ferrer y Esteve (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Spanish Favorites for Classic Guitar
  - Domenico Cimarosa (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. V, No. 3, Fall 1952 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. VI, No. 1, Spring 1953 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. VII, No. 3, Fall 1954 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. VIII, No. 1, Spring 1955 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XIV, No. 1, Spring 1961 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XIV, No. 3, Fall 1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XVIII, No. 4, September 1961 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XIX, No. 1, December 1961 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XIX, No. 4, September 1962 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XX, No. 2, Spring 1963 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society: Vol. XXI, No. 3, Summer 1964 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 1, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 2, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 3, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 5, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 6, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 7, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 8, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 10, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 11, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 12, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 13, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 14, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 15, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 16, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 18, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 19, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 20, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 22, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 23, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 24, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 25, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 26, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 27, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 28, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 29, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 30, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 30, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 31, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 32, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 33, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 35, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 36, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 37, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 38, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 39, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 40, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 41, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 42, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 43, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 44, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 45, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 46, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 48, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 50, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 51, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 52, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 53, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 54, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Guitar Review: No. 61, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Etude - The Music Magazine: Vol. 73, No. 11, November 1955 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Etude - The Music Magazine: Vol. 73, No. 12, December 1955 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Etude - The Music Magazine: Vol. 74, No. 1, January 1956 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 13, No. 3 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 13, No. 4 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 14, No. 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 14, No. 2 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 14, No. 3 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 14, No. 4 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Music Studio News: Vol. 14, No. 6 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Guitar and Lute: No. 7, September 1978 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Guitar and Lute: No. 16, January 1981 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Guitar and Lute: No. 17, April 1981 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Guitar and Lute: No. 21, March 1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fretts, June-July 1958 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Fretts, February-March 1959 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fretts, June-July 1959 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Fretts, July-August 1959 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Fretts, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Vol. 3
  - Fretts, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Vol. 5
  - Fretts, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Soundboard: Vol. III, No. 2, May 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Soundboard: Vol. IV, No. 4, November 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Soundboard: Vol. V, No. 1, February 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VI, No. 1, February 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VI, No. 2, May 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VI, No. 3, August 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VI, No. 4, November 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VII, No. 4, November 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VIII, No. 1, February 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Soundboard: Vol. VIII, No. 4, November 1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Soundboard: Vol. IX, No. 3, Fall 1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Soundboard: Vol. IX, No. 4, Winter 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter: Vol. XIV, No. 4, October 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter: Vol. XVI, No. 2, May 1981 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 1, No. 5 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 1, No. 6 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 1, No. 7 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 3, December 1948 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 4, January 1948 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 5, February 1949 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 5, March 1949 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    (editorial error)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 6, April 1949 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 2, No. 7, May 1949 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 3, No. 5, November-December 1950 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 4, No. 1, January 1951 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 4, No. 3, April-May 1951 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 4, No. 5, September-October 1951 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 4, No. 6, November-December 1951 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 5, No. 1, January-February 1952 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 5, No. 2, March-April 1952 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 5, No. 3, May-June 1952 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 6, No. 2, November-December 1952 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 6, No. 5, April 1953 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 6, No. 6, May-June 1953 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 7, No. 1, October 1953 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 7, No. 3, February-March 1954 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 7, No. 4, April-June 1954 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 8, No. 1, November 1954 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 9, No. 2, December 1954 - January 1955 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 9, No. 3, February-April 1955 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 11, No. 3, March-May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - SCG Bulletin, March 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 12, No. 3, April-May 1959 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 12, No. 4, Summer 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 13, No. 1, Fall 1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 13 No. 2, Winter 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 13, No. 3, Winter-Spring 1960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 13, No. 4, Spring-Summer 1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 18, No. 1, Summer-Fall 1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 18, No. 2, Fall-Winter 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 18, No. 3, Winter 1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 19, No. 1, Summer-Fall 1965 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 20, No. 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Fall 1966 - Winter 1967
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 20, No. 3, Winter-Spring 1967 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 21, No. 2, Fall 1967 - Winter 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 21, No. 3, Winter-Spring 1968 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 21, No. 4, Spring-Summer 1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 22, No. 1, Summer-Fall 1968 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 22, No. 4, Spring-Summer 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 23, No. 2, Fall 1969 - Winter 1970 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 23, No. 3, Winter-Spring 1970 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 24, No. 1, Summer-Fall 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - SCG Bulletin: Vol. 24, No. 2, Winter 1970 - Spring 1971 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Great Music: Announcing the Coming Selection (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Great Music: Announcing the Coming Selection (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Great Music: Announcing the Coming Selection (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Thomas Tapper (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Child's Own Book of Great Musicians - Handel
  - Thomas Tapper (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Child's Own Book of Great Musicians - Haydn
  - Thomas Tapper (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Child's Own Book of Great Musicians - Liszt
  - Notes: The Quarterly Journal of the Music Library Association, Vol. XXIII, No. 3, March 1967 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Journal of the Lute Society of America, Inc. - Vol. X, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Peter Danner, editor
  - BMG Banjo Mandolin Guitar - Vol. XLVII, No. 542, June 1950 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Journal of the Lute Society of America, Inc. - No. 1, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Repertoire - Vol. 1, No. 1, October 1951 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Stock Order Blank, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    A selected list from catalogs of Belwin-Mills Corp, Edward B. Marks Music Corp., MCA Music.
  - Editions Orphee: Preliminary Catalogue, September 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Descriptive Checklist of Selected Manuscripts in the Monastaries of Mount Athos (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - International Inventory of Musical Sources: Report of the Joint US Committee on Activities to January 1, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Prepared by Wayne D. Shirley
  - Guitar Newsletter - Vol. 2, No. 4, November 1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - FIGA News: Official Publication of the Fretted Instrument Guild of America, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Cover page only
  - Rosetter - Vol. 2, No. 12, December 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Bulletin of the National Association for Music Therapy, Inc. Vol. VIII, No. 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Classic Guitar Journal No. 36, January-April 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Boston Classical Guitar Society Newsletter, November 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Guitar Vol. 1, No. 16, June 1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Seattle Classic Guitar Society Vol. 15, No. 5, June 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Seattle Classic Guitar Society Vol. 15, No. 6, September 1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Teacher Listings as of January 1958 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Prepared by the Society of the Classical Guitar
  - Bulletin of the Philharmonic Society of Guitarists (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Art of True Living: Treatise No. 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Edwin J. Dingle, author
  - Guitarra Magazine, January-February 1967 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Guitarra Magazine, November-December 1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Hendley-Kaspar School of Musical Art, Season 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - The Classical Guitarist Vol. 4, No. 3, February-March 1968 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Music Studio News Vol. 11, No. 6, November-December 1954 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Seattle Classical Guitar Society July Bulletin, Vol. VI, No. 7 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Seattle Classical Guitar Society July Bulletin, Vol. VII, No. 7 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - The Rosette - Vol. 2, No. 6, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - The Rosette - Vol. 3, No. 2, February 1974 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - SCG Bulletin: Montoya, His Guitars, His Triumphs and His Sorrows (Box 16, Folder 29)
    article
  - The Guitar Review, ca. Fall 1970 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Andres Segovia (Box 16, Folder 31)
    The Guitar and Myself
  - Music History of Greece: Chapter 1 - From 776 BC to 2nd Century AD (Box 16, Folder 32)
    Kleon Raptakis, author (excerpted from unknown magazine)
  - "Doina": Romanian Folk Ballet of Bucharest (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Program, Columbia Artists Mgmt.
  - Andres Segovia Exhibit, January 15, 1978 - February 15, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Ronald C. Purcell, Oviatt Library, California State University, Northridge Program
  - Sophocles Papas Biographical Material (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Book
  - Sophocles Papas Biographical Material (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Clippings
  - Catalogs - Indexes (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Columbia School of Music (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Miscellaneous
  - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Brief Biographies of Composers (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Proposals (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - WGS Oral History (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Tassantino Printing Company Corporate Papers (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Personal (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Programs, Reviews, Announcements (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Society Informtaion (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Term Papers/Reports (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Manuscripts - Sophocles Papas (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Method for the Classical Guitar (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Manuscript by Sophocles Papas
  - Manuscripts - Elisabeth Papas-Smith (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Manuscripts - Arranger and Transcriber Known (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Manuscripts - Composer Known (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Manuscripts - Arranger and Transcriber Unknown (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Manuscripts - Composer Unknown (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - David Arnold (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Jose de Azpiazu (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Walter Kaye Bauer (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Carver Blanchard (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Carulli Ferd (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Alan Dodd (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Marvin Falcon (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Patrico Galindo (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - John K. Griggs (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Leonard Handler (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Richard C. Harrison (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Don Keefer (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Arthur Larson (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Newton C. S. Leao (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Arthur Levering (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - John E. Marlow (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Manuscripts - Philip Morimitso (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Marvin W. Muse (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Allan Neidle (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Bret Orton (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - German Salinas (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Andres Segovia (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Bob Sheeley (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Robert Shieby (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Thomas Simmons (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - J. Morgan Smith, Jr. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - James Stewart (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Mareno Torroba (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - George Yeatman (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Published Compositions - Complete (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Published Composition - Incomplete (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Dance of the Shadows - "Dinorah" (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Ethnikos Ymnos - Greek National Hymn (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Evocaciones Criollas (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Concerto in D (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Arabesque (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Mia Amorita (Danza Mexicana) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Nocturne (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Valse Triste (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Alborada (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Sonatine (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Serenado No. 1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Kleine Overture (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Sonate No. 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Overture No. 1 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Nr. 27/28 Quartett fur 4 Gitarren (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Andante (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Die Gitarre in Der Haus (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Part - Songs for Mixed Voices (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Serenade Concertante en Trio (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Dowland Songs for Guitar and Voice (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Divertissement (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 29)